# **Claude Sortwell**

7 Rusmey Crescent Dundas Valley, NSW 2117 0406 382 193 claude.sortwell@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

Comprehensive knowledge of customer service, sales methods and stock management. Involved and engaged in diagnosing and fixing customer problems, with years of experience in doing so, while also providing an inviting and enjoyable customer service experience. Extensive knowledge in computer systems, and willingness to learn computer systems.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Bunnings**, Rydalmere — Special Orders Team Member

May 2019 - November 2019

Received and followed pick sheets to gather merchandise for customer orders. Followed up with customers about unresolved issues. Working directly with trade accounts and fulfilling their orders/enquiries. Delivered exceptional customer service to every customer by leveraging extensive knowledge of products and services and creating welcoming, positive experiences. Ensured superior customer experience by addressing customer concerns, demonstrating empathy and resolving problems swiftly. Responded to customer requests for products and services.

## **Bunnings**, Rydalmere — Shipping Dock Team Member

November 2018 - May 2019

Signing and counting delivery orders, entering them into electronic goods system. Moving pallets of stock with manual and electric pallet jack. Unpacking pallets of stock and breaking them down into each and individual store department. Building pallets of stock, wrapping and strapping the pallets for shipping or top stock.

## **McDonalds**, Rydalmere — *Crew Member*

January 2017 - November 2018

Receive payment by cash, credit cards, vouchers, or automatic debits. Issue receipts, refunds, credits, or change due to customers. Assist customers by providing information and resolving their complaints. Check with customers to ensure that they are enjoying their meals and take action to correct any problems. Read food order slips or receive verbal instructions as to food required by patron, and prepare and cook food according to instructions. Greeted customers entering establishments.

## **SKILLS**

**Customer Service** 

**Customer Sales** 

**Refunds and Payments** 

**Problem Resolution** 

Technology Knowledge

Computer Problem Diagnosing

Fixing Technology Problems

Experience with Point of Sales Systems

#### **CERTIFICATES**

First Aid Certificate

White Card

1st in Entertainment Industry

1st in Software Development and Design

3rd in Mathematics General

## **REFERENCES**

**Daniel Fuchs** 

Shift Manager McDonald's 0401287740

Natalie

Bunnings Manager 0421431979

## **EDUCATION**

**Macquarie University** 

January 2019 - Present Software Engineering

**Marist College Eastwood** 

January 2013 - Sep 2018 HSC - ATAR